<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<!-- Link XML to XSLT stylesheet -->
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="books.xsl"?>

<!-- Link XML to DTD for validation -->
<!DOCTYPE bookshop SYSTEM "bookshop.dtd">

<!-- Root element containing all books -->
<bookshop>
    <book id="b1">
        <title>The Mountain Is You</title>
        <author>Brianna Wiest</author>
        <genre>Self-Help / Psychology</genre>
        <price>750.00</price>
        <year>2020</year>
        <isbn>978-0-306-40600-7</isbn>
        <quantity>10</quantity>
        <image>images/the-mountain-is-you.png</image>
        <link>../contact.html</link>
        <description>This is a book about self-sabotage. Why we do it, when we do it, and how to stop doing it—for good. Coexisting but conflicting needs create self-sabotaging behaviors. This is why we resist efforts to change, often until they feel completely futile. But by extracting crucial insight from our most damaging habits, building emotional intelligence by better understanding our brains and bodies, releasing past experiences at a cellular level, and learning to act as our highest potential future selves, we can step out of our own way and into our potential. For centuries, the mountain has been used as a metaphor for the big challenges we face, especially ones that seem impossible to overcome. To scale our mountains, we actually have to do the deep internal work of excavating trauma, building resilience, and adjusting how we show up for the climb. In the end, it is not the mountain we master, but ourselves.</description>
    </book>
    
    <book id="b2">
        <title>Atomic Habits</title>
        <author>James Clear</author>
        <genre>Self-Help / Psychology</genre>
        <price>935.00</price>
        <year>2018</year>
        <isbn>978-0-306-40601-7</isbn>
        <quantity>18</quantity>
        <image>images/atomic-habits.jpg</image>
        <link>../contact.html</link>
        <description>No matter your goals, Atomic Habits offers a proven framework for improving—every day. James Clear, one of the world's leading experts on habit formation, reveals practical strategies that will teach you exactly how to form good habits, break bad ones, and master the tiny behaviors that lead to remarkable results.</description>
    </book>
    

    <book id="b3">
        <title>The Psychology Of Money</title>
        <author>Morgan Housel</author>
        <genre>Self-Help / Psychology</genre>
        <price>1501.50</price>
        <year>2020</year>
        <isbn>978-0-306-40602-7</isbn>
        <quantity>20</quantity>
        <image>images/the-psychology-of-money.jpg</image>
        <link>../contact.html</link>
        <description>Doing well with money isn’t necessarily about what you know. It’s about how you behave. And behavior is hard to teach, even to really smart people. In The Psychology of Money, award-winning author Morgan Housel shares 19 short stories exploring the different ways people think about money and teaches you how to make better sense of one of life’s most important topics.</description>
    </book>
    
    <book id="b4">
        <title>The Let Them Theory</title>
        <author>Mel Robbins</author>
        <genre>Self-Help / Psychology</genre>
        <price>1260.05</price>
        <year>2024</year>
        <isbn>978-0-306-40603-7</isbn>
        <quantity>22</quantity>
        <image>images/the-let-them-theory.jpg</image>
        <link>../contact.html</link>
        <description>If you've ever felt stuck, overwhelmed, or frustrated with where you are, the problem isn't you. The problem is the power you give to other people. Two simple words—Let Them—will set you free. Free from the opinions, drama, and judgments of others. Free from the exhausting cycle of trying to manage everything and everyone around you. The Let Them Theory puts the power to create a life you love back in your hands—and this book will show you exactly how to do it.</description>
    </book>
    
    <book id="b5">
        <title>The Subtle Art Of Not Giving A F*ck</title>
        <author>Mark Manson</author>
        <genre>Self-Help / Psychology</genre>
        <price>1300.00</price>
        <year>2016</year>
        <isbn>978-0-306-40604-7</isbn>
        <quantity>10</quantity>
        <image>images/the-subtle-art-of-not-giving-a-fuck.jpg</image>
        <link>../contact.html</link>
        <description>There are only so many things we can give a f*k about so we need to figure out which ones really matter, Manson makes clear. While money is nice, caring about what you do with your life is better, because true wealth is about experience. A much-needed grab-you-by-the-shoulders-and-look-you-in-the-eye moment of real-talk, filled with entertaining stories and profane, ruthless humor, The Subtle Art of Not Giving a F*k is a refreshing slap for a generation to help them lead contented, grounded lives.</description>
    </book>
    
    <book id="b6">
        <title>Ikigai</title>
        <author>Héctor García and Francesc Miralles</author>
        <genre>Self-Help / Psychology</genre>
        <price>550</price>
        <year>2016</year>
        <isbn>978-0-306-40605-7</isbn>
        <quantity>12</quantity>
        <image>images/ikigai.jpg</image>
        <link>../contact.html</link>
        <description>According to the Japanese, everyone has an ikigai—a reason for living. And according to the residents of the Japanese village with the world’s longest-living people, finding it is the key to a happier and longer life. Having a strong sense of ikigai—where what you love, what you’re good at, what you can get paid for, and what the world needs all overlap—means that each day is infused with meaning. It’s the reason we get up in the morning. It’s also the reason many Japanese never really retire: they remain active and work at what they enjoy, because they’ve found a real purpose in life.</description>
    </book>
    
    <book id="b7">
        <title>Everything Is F*cked</title>
        <author>Mark Manson</author>
        <genre>Self-Help / Psychology</genre>
        <price>1550</price>
        <year>2019</year>
        <isbn>978-0-306-40606-7</isbn>
        <quantity>11</quantity>
        <image>images/everything-is-fucked.png</image>
        <link>../contact.html</link>
        <description>In Everything Is F*cked, Manson turns his gaze from the inevitable flaws within each individual self to the endless calamities taking place in the world around us. Drawing from psychological research and philosophy, he examines faith, happiness, freedom, hope, money, entertainment, and the internet.</description>
    </book>
    
    <book id="b8">
        <title>The Silent Patient</title>
        <author>Alex Michaelides</author>
        <genre>Mystery</genre>
        <price>900.00</price>
        <year>2019</year>
        <isbn>978-0-306-40607-7</isbn>
        <quantity>14</quantity>
        <image>images/the_silent_patient.jpg</image>
        <link>../contact.html</link>
        <description>Theo Faber is a criminal psychotherapist who has waited a long time for the opportunity to work with Alicia. His determination to get her to talk and unravel the mystery of why she shot her husband takes him down a twisting path into his own motivations—a search for the truth that threatens to consume him.</description>
    </book>
    
    <book id="b9">
        <title>A Good Girl's Guide To Murder</title>
        <author>Holly Jackson</author>
        <genre>Mystery</genre>
        <price>600.00</price>
        <year>2019</year>
        <isbn>978-0-306-40608-7</isbn>
        <quantity>8</quantity>
        <image>images/a-good-girls-guide-to-murder.jpg</image>
        <link>../contact.html</link>
        <description>The case is closed. Five years ago, schoolgirl Andie Bell was murdered by Sal Singh. The police know he did it. Everyone in town knows he did it. But Pippa Fitz-Amobi isn't so sure. When she chooses the case as the topic for her final project, she starts to uncover secrets that someone in town desperately wants to stay hidden.</description>
    </book>
    
    <book id="b10">
        <title>Good Girl, Bad Blood</title>
        <author>Holly Jackson</author>
        <genre>Mystery</genre>
        <price>650.00</price>
        <year>2020</year>
        <isbn>978-0-306-40609-7</isbn>
        <quantity>15</quantity>
        <image>images/good-girl-bad-blood.jpg</image>
        <link>../contact.html</link>
        <description>Pip is not a detective anymore. Yet when someone she knows goes missing, she has to break that promise. Jamie Reynolds has disappeared, and the police won't do anything about it. Pip uncovers more of her town's dark secrets, and this time everyone is listening.</description>
    </book>
    
    <book id="b11">
        <title>One Of Us Is Lying</title>
        <author>Karen M. McManus</author>
        <genre>Mystery</genre>
        <price>740.00</price>
        <year>2017</year>
        <isbn>978-0-306-40610-7</isbn>
        <quantity>19</quantity>
        <image>images/one-of-us-is-lying.jpg</image>
        <link>../contact.html</link>
        <description>Five students walk into detention. Only four walk out alive. Simon, the creator of Bayview High's notorious gossip app, dies before the end of detention, and all four classmates become suspects in his murder. Everyone has secrets. What matters is how far you would go to protect them.</description>
    </book>
    
    <book id="b12">
        <title>We Were Liars</title>
        <author>E. Lockhart</author>
        <genre>Mystery</genre>
        <price>450.00</price>
        <year>2014</year>
        <isbn>978-0-306-40611-7</isbn>
        <quantity>12</quantity>
        <image>images/we-were-liars.jpg</image>
        <link>../contact.html</link>
        <description>A beautiful and distinguished family. A private island. A brilliant, damaged girl. A group of four friends—the Liars—whose friendship turns destructive. A secret. Lies upon lies. True love. The truth.</description>
    </book>
    
    <book id="b13">
        <title>Fearless</title>
        <author>Lauren Roberts</author>
        <genre>Fantasy Romance</genre>
        <price>650.00</price>
        <year>2025</year>
        <isbn>978-0-306-40612-7</isbn>
        <quantity>18</quantity>
        <image>images/fearless.jpg</image>
        <link>../contact.html</link>
        <description>With a decision looming, Paedyn battles between her head, her heart, and the hidden trials she now faces. Through it all, Kai Azer fights to call her his, even if it means defying his king. Are vows strong enough to unite a kingdom? Or will betrayal break them?</description>
    </book>
    
    <book id="b14">
        <title>Powerless</title>
        <author>Lauren Roberts</author>
        <genre>Fantasy Romance</genre>
        <price>700.00</price>
        <year>2023</year>
        <isbn>978-0-306-40613-7</isbn>
        <quantity>14</quantity>
        <image>images/powerless.jpg</image>
        <link>../contact.html</link>
        <description>Surviving in the slums as an Ordinary is no simple task. Paedyn poses as a Psychic to stay alive, but when she saves one of Ilya's princes, she is thrown into the Purging Trials—a brutal competition meant for the Elites whose powers she does not possess.</description>
    </book>
    
    <book id="b15">
        <title>Reckless</title>
        <author>Lauren Roberts</author>
        <genre>Fantasy Romance</genre>
        <price>750.00</price>
        <year>2024</year>
        <isbn>978-0-306-40614-7</isbn>
        <quantity>17</quantity>
        <image>images/reckless.jpg</image>
        <link>../contact.html</link>
        <description>The kingdom of Ilya is in turmoil. After surviving the Purging Trials, Paedyn Gray has killed the King and started a Resistance. Now she is running from Kai Azer, who has vowed to find her and bring her to justice, even though duty and desire are at war within him.</description>
    </book>
    
    <book id="b16">
        <title>The Cruel Prince</title>
        <author>Holly Black</author>
        <genre>Fantasy Romance</genre>
        <price>600.00</price>
        <year>2018</year>
        <isbn>978-0-306-40615-7</isbn>
        <quantity>20</quantity>
        <image>images/the-cruel-prince.jpg</image>
        <link>../contact.html</link>
        <description>Jude was seven when her parents were murdered and she and her sisters were taken to live in the High Court of Faerie. Ten years later, she wants nothing more than to belong there, even though she is mortal. To win a place at court, she must defy Prince Cardan and face the consequences.</description>
    </book>
    
    <book id="b17">
        <title>Onyx Storm</title>
        <author>Rebecca Yarros</author>
        <genre>Fantasy Romance</genre>
        <price>800.00</price>
        <year>2025</year>
        <isbn>978-0-306-40616-7</isbn>
        <quantity>12</quantity>
        <image>images/onyx-storm.jpg</image>
        <link>../contact.html</link>
        <description>After nearly eighteen months at Basgiath War College, Violet Sorrengail knows there is no more time for lessons. She must journey beyond the failing wards to seek allies from unfamiliar lands and uncover a truth that may save everything she loves.</description>
    </book>
    
    <book id="b18">
        <title>Fourth Wing</title>
        <author>Rebecca Yarros</author>
        <genre>Fantasy Romance</genre>
        <price>650.00</price>
        <year>2023</year>
        <isbn>978-0-306-40617-7</isbn>
        <quantity>17</quantity>
        <image>images/fourth-wing.jpg</image>
        <link>../contact.html</link>
        <description>Enter the brutal and elite world of a war college for dragon riders. Violet Sorrengail was supposed to live a quiet life among books, but instead must compete in a deadly Riders Quadrant where dragons, enemies, and secrets threaten her survival every day.</description>
    </book>
    
    <book id="b19">
        <title>The Wicked King</title>
        <author>Holly Black</author>
        <genre>Fantasy Romance</genre>
        <price>550.00</price>
        <year>2019</year>
        <isbn>978-0-306-40619-7</isbn>
        <quantity>21</quantity>
        <image>images/the-wicked-king.jpg</image>
        <link>../contact.html</link>
        <description>After the revelation that Oak is the heir to Faerie, Jude must keep her brother safe while controlling the wicked king, Cardan. But the politics of Faerie are dangerous, and betrayal threatens everything she loves.</description>
    </book>
    
    <book id="b20">
        <title>The Queen Of Nothing</title>
        <author>Holly Black</author>
        <genre>Fantasy Romance</genre>
        <price>575.00</price>
        <year>2019</year>
        <isbn>978-0-306-40620-7</isbn>
        <quantity>18</quantity>
        <image>images/the-queen-of-nothing.jpg</image>
        <link>../contact.html</link>
        <description>Jude, now the exiled mortal Queen of Faerie, is powerless after Cardan's betrayal. When opportunity arrives, she risks venturing back into Elfhame, where war is brewing and she must choose between her ambition and her humanity.</description>
    </book>
    
    <book id="b21">
        <title>A Touch of Darkness</title>
        <author>Scarlett St. Clair</author>
        <genre>Fantasy Romance</genre>
        <price>750.00</price>
        <year>2019</year>
        <isbn>978-0-306-40635-7</isbn>
        <quantity>16</quantity>
        <image>images/a-touch-of-darkness.jpg</image>
        <link>../contact.html</link>
        <description>Persephone is the Goddess of Spring by title only. After moving to New Athens, she hopes to live quietly as a mortal journalist. But after a chance encounter with Hades, she is forced into a contract that may cost her freedom—and her heart.</description>
    </book>
    
    <book id="b22">
        <title>Twisted Love</title>
        <author>Ana Huang</author>
        <genre>Romance Fiction</genre>
        <price>525.00</price>
        <year>2021</year>
        <isbn>978-0-306-40621-7</isbn>
        <quantity>28</quantity>
        <image>images/twisted-love.jpg</image>
        <link>../contact.html</link>
        <description>Alex Volkov has a heart of ice, but when he is forced to look after his best friend's sister, Ava Chen, he begins to feel something dangerous. Their forbidden romance unleashes secrets that could destroy them both.</description>
    </book>
    
    <book id="b23">
        <title>Twisted Lies</title>
        <author>Ana Huang</author>
        <genre>Romance Fiction</genre>
        <price>600.00</price>
        <year>2022</year>
        <isbn>978-0-306-40622-7</isbn>
        <quantity>20</quantity>
        <image>images/twisted-lies.jpg</image>
        <link>../contact.html</link>
        <description>Christian Harper is charming, deadly, and smart enough to hide it. Stella Alonso is sweet, shy, and guarded. When a threat from her past pushes her toward him, a dangerous arrangement grows into something far more intense.</description>
    </book>
    
    <book id="b24">
        <title>King of Wrath</title>
        <author>Ana Huang</author>
        <genre>Romance Fiction</genre>
        <price>575.00</price>
        <year>2022</year>
        <isbn>978-0-306-40623-7</isbn>
        <quantity>19</quantity>
        <image>images/king-of-wrath.jpg</image>
        <link>../contact.html</link>
        <description>Dante Russo thrives on control, but blackmail forces him into an engagement with Vivian Lau. He plans to destroy the arrangement, but keeping his distance becomes harder when desire and duty collide.</description>
    </book>
    
    <book id="b25">
        <title>King Of Greed</title>
        <author>Ana Huang</author>
        <genre>Romance Fiction</genre>
        <price>600.00</price>
        <year>2023</year>
        <isbn>978-0-306-40624-7</isbn>
        <quantity>18</quantity>
        <image>images/king-of-greed.jpg</image>
        <link>../contact.html</link>
        <description>Dominic Davenport built an empire but drove away the only person who loved him for himself. Alessandra Davenport finally chooses herself, and Dominic must fight for the marriage he nearly destroyed.</description>
    </book>
    
    <book id="b26">
        <title>The Fine Print</title>
        <author>Lauren Asher</author>
        <genre>Romance Fiction</genre>
        <price>500.00</price>
        <year>2021</year>
        <isbn>978-0-306-40625-7</isbn>
        <quantity>12</quantity>
        <image>images/the-fine-print.jpg</image>
        <link>../contact.html</link>
        <description>Rowan Kane is in the business of creating fairy tales, but hiring Zahra for Dreamland changes everything. Their professional arrangement spirals into something personal, and secrets threaten the possibility of a happy ending.</description>
    </book>
    
    <book id="b27">
        <title>Love Redesigned</title>
        <author>Lauren Asher</author>
        <genre>Romance Fiction</genre>
        <price>600.00</price>
        <year>2023</year>
        <isbn>978-0-306-40626-7</isbn>
        <quantity>16</quantity>
        <image>images/love-redesigned.jpg</image>
        <link>../contact.html</link>
        <description>Julian Lopez and Dahlia Muñoz are childhood rivals forced into a renovation project together. Their temporary truce grows complicated as old emotions and undeniable attraction return.</description>
    </book>
    
    <book id="b28">
        <title>Terms and Conditions</title>
        <author>Lauren Asher</author>
        <genre>Romance Fiction</genre>
        <price>600.00</price>
        <year>2022</year>
        <isbn>978-0-306-40627-7</isbn>
        <quantity>20</quantity>
        <image>images/terms-and-conditions.jpg</image>
        <link>../contact.html</link>
        <description>Declan needs a wife to fulfill his grandfather's inheritance clause, and his assistant Iris offers the perfect fake solution. But when their contract starts to feel real, both risk getting hurt.</description>
    </book>
    
    <book id="b29">
        <title>Hunting Adeline</title>
        <author>H.D. Carlton</author>
        <genre>Dark Romance</genre>
        <price>1150.00</price>
        <year>2022</year>
        <isbn>978-0-306-40628-7</isbn>
        <quantity>20</quantity>
        <image>images/hunting-adeline.jpg</image>
        <link>../contact.html</link>
        <description>The Diamond Death walks alongside me, but the reaper is no match for me. Trapped in a world of monsters, Adeline fights to survive while the predator who hunts her tears apart the world to find her.</description>
    </book>
    
    <book id="b30">
        <title>Haunting Adeline</title>
        <author>H.D. Carlton</author>
        <genre>Dark Romance</genre>
        <price>1300.00</price>
        <year>2021</year>
        <isbn>978-0-306-40629-7</isbn>
        <quantity>21</quantity>
        <image>images/haunting-adeline.jpg</image>
        <link>../contact.html</link>
        <description>The Manipulator can bend emotions. The Shadow cannot stay away. Their obsession grows darker and more dangerous as desire, fear, and possession become impossible to separate.</description>
    </book>
    
    <book id="b31">
        <title>God of Malice</title>
        <author>Rina Kent</author>
        <genre>Dark Romance</genre>
        <price>800.00</price>
        <year>2022</year>
        <isbn>978-0-306-40630-7</isbn>
        <quantity>21</quantity>
        <image>images/god-of-malice.jpg</image>
        <link>../contact.html</link>
        <description>I caught the attention of a monster. Killian Carson is cold-blooded, manipulative, and savage, and once he sees me, escape becomes impossible.</description>
    </book>
    
    <book id="b32">
        <title>God of Pain</title>
        <author>Rina Kent</author>
        <genre>Dark Romance</genre>
        <price>800.00</price>
        <year>2022</year>
        <isbn>978-0-306-40631-7</isbn>
        <quantity>21</quantity>
        <image>images/god-of-pain.jpg</image>
        <link>../contact.html</link>
        <description>Annika Volkov longed for the wrong man. Creighton King is silent, dangerous, and emotionally unreachable, but their conflict awakens something destructive in them both.</description>
    </book>
    
    <book id="b33">
        <title>God of Wrath</title>
        <author>Rina Kent</author>
        <genre>Dark Romance</genre>
        <price>800.00</price>
        <year>2022</year>
        <isbn>978-0-306-40632-7</isbn>
        <quantity>20</quantity>
        <image>images/god-of-wrath.jpg</image>
        <link>../contact.html</link>
        <description>When Cecily Knight sneaks into the Heathen Club on behalf of a rival gang, she catches the eye of Jeremy Volkov, the ruthless heir to the Russian Bratva, who wants to claim her for himself.</description>
    </book>
    
    <book id="b34">
        <title>The Sweetest Oblivion</title>
        <author>Danielle Lori</author>
        <genre>Dark Romance</genre>
        <price>1050.00</price>
        <year>2018</year>
        <isbn>978-0-306-40633-7</isbn>
        <quantity>13</quantity>
        <image>images/the-sweetest-oblivion.jpg</image>
        <link>../contact.html</link>
        <description>Elena Abelli is a romantic at heart living in the mafia underworld. When her sister is arranged to marry Nicolas Russo, Elena finds herself drawn to the one man she should never want.</description>
    </book>
    
    <book id="b35">
        <title>The Maddest Obsession</title>
        <author>Danielle Lori</author>
        <genre>Dark Romance</genre>
        <price>1025.00</price>
        <year>2019</year>
        <isbn>978-0-306-40634-7</isbn>
        <quantity>13</quantity>
        <image>images/the-maddest-obsession.jpg</image>
        <link>../contact.html</link>
        <description>Gianna wears chaos like glitter, while Christian Allister is cold order personified. Their lives intertwine over years of rivalry, fascination, and attraction neither can control.</description>
    </book>
    
    <book id="b36">
        <title>The Sinner</title>
        <author>Shantel Tessier</author>
        <genre>Dark Romance</genre>
        <price>1280.00</price>
        <year>2022</year>
        <isbn>978-0-306-40636-7</isbn>
        <quantity>16</quantity>
        <image>images/the-sinner.jpg</image>
        <link>../contact.html</link>
        <description>Raised in a world of money and secret power, she falls for Easton Bradley Sinnett—Sin—a man whose darkness wrecks her in the worst way, yet she cannot stop craving him.</description>
    </book>
    
    <book id="b37">
        <title>Priest</title>
        <author>Sierra Simone</author>
        <genre>Dark Romance</genre>
        <price>550.00</price>
        <year>2022</year>
        <isbn>978-0-306-40637-7</isbn>
        <quantity>18</quantity>
        <image>images/the-priest.jpg</image>
        <link>../contact.html</link>
        <description>Tyler Bell has followed every rule of priesthood until Poppy Danforth enters his confessional and his forbidden thoughts become impossible to silence.</description>
    </book>
    
    <book id="b38">
        <title>The Hybrid Prince</title>
        <author>Tui T. Sutherland</author>
        <genre>Children</genre>
        <price>850.00</price>
        <year>2026</year>
        <isbn>978-0-306-40638-7</isbn>
        <quantity>23</quantity>
        <image>images/the-hybrid-prince.jpg</image>
        <link>../contact.html</link>
        <description>In The Hybrid Prince, MudWing siblings Umber and Sora flee Jade Mountain Academy after an explosion set by Sora kills two students. They fly across desolate islands trying to survive and escape the consequences.</description>
    </book>
    
    <book id="b39">
        <title>Escaping Peril</title>
        <author>Tui T. Sutherland</author>
        <genre>Children</genre>
        <price>850.00</price>
        <year>2025</year>
        <isbn>978-0-306-40639-7</isbn>
        <quantity>21</quantity>
        <image>images/escaping-peril-the-graphic-novel.jpeg</image>
        <link>../contact.html</link>
        <description>Peril, a dragon known for her deadly firescales, must stop Queen Scarlet from threatening Jade Mountain Academy while questioning her own loyalty and worth.</description>
    </book>
    
    <book id="b40">
        <title>Better Than A Touchdown</title>
        <author>Jalen Hurts</author>
        <genre>Children</genre>
        <price>700.00</price>
        <year>2026</year>
        <isbn>978-0-306-40640-7</isbn>
        <quantity>18</quantity>
        <image>images/better-than-a-touchdown.jpg</image>
        <link>../contact.html</link>
        <description>From Philadelphia Eagles quarterback Jalen Hurts comes an empowering story about friendship, community, and the power of teamwork. Jalen is excited for the new school year because he finally gets to try out for the football team.</description>
    </book>
    
    <book id="b41">
        <title>The Adventures Of Tubby Nugget</title>
        <author>Jenine Pastores and Josh Jackson</author>
        <genre>Children</genre>
        <price>890.00</price>
        <year>2026</year>
        <isbn>978-0-306-40641-7</isbn>
        <quantity>23</quantity>
        <image>images/the-adventures-of-tubby-nugget.jpg</image>
        <link>../contact.html</link>
        <description>Tubby refuses the dunking ceremony, a tradition on Planet Nüg that turns small nugs into serious adults, choosing instead a fun, creative life full of imagination.</description>
    </book>
    
    <book id="b42">
        <title>Mother Bruce</title>
        <author>Ryan T. Higgins</author>
        <genre>Children</genre>
        <price>500.00</price>
        <year>2015</year>
        <isbn>978-0-306-40642-7</isbn>
        <quantity>20</quantity>
        <image>images/mother-bruce.jpg</image>
        <link>../contact.html</link>
        <description>Bruce the bear likes to keep to himself and eat eggs. But when his hard-boiled goose eggs hatch into goslings who think he is their mother, everything changes.</description>
    </book>
</bookshop>
